export const jsQuizz = {
    questions: [
    {
        question: "One of the popular sharks’ company also a partner for Unmaad 2023.",
        photo: "",
        type: "TEXT",
        correctAnswer: "boat",
    },
    {
        question: "Let the _______ saga continue. ",
        photo: "",
        type: "TEXT",
        correctAnswer: "celestial",
    },
    {
        question: "Lets hear the beat drop.",
        photo: "",
        type: "TEXT",
        correctAnswer: "footloose",
    },
    {
        question: "Founder and director of Mrs. India Inc.",
        photo: "",
        type: "TEXT",
        correctAnswer: "mohinisharma",
    },
    {
        question: "Duet singing event. ",
        photo: "",
        type: "TEXT",
        correctAnswer: "bandish",
    },
    {
        question: "Filmfare awardee and singer of a famous song in ‘Mismatched’.",
        photo: "",
        type: "TEXT",
        correctAnswer: "raghavchaitanya",
    },
    {
        question: "Online Poker Tournament partner.",
        photo: "",
        type: "TEXT",
        correctAnswer: "pokerbaazi",
    },
    {
        question: "Unmaad’s legacy event being conducted in Vega City mall this year.",
        photo: "",
        type: "TEXT",
        correctAnswer: "flashmob",
    },
    {
        question: "MTV Splitsvilla and Roadies fame. ",
        photo: "",
        type: "TEXT",
        correctAnswer: "soundous",
    },
    {
        question: "One of games that will be played during Gamethon.",
        photo: "",
        type: "TEXT",
        correctAnswer: "fifa",
    },
    ]
    
  };
  
  export const resultInitalState = {
    score: 0,
    correctAnswers: 0,
    wrongAnswers: 0,
  };